heyo you youtubers out there backyard
experimenter here wanted to do a video
quick video on my space-time antenna I
haven't been seeing much out there on
YouTube about it anymore I don't know if
everybody quit working on it or or what
but I wanted to do some experimenting
with it so I called this up it's 14 feet
each coil each cone is 14 feet of 4
gauge grounding table that you ground a
breaker box with and I call that up per
video I watched on YouTube about how to
wind a Bashar free energy space-time
antenna and believe was the name of it
something like that and that's what I
come up with there is no reason in
particular why one call is white and the
other ones not I just got lazy when I
was insulating it and didn't finish
insulating the other one but I may have
to because as you can see I had
electrical tape right here where my coil
was making contact with my tetrahedron
because I was getting an arc through the
cardboard from the aluminum foil that
lines the outside of my tetrahedron and
will set this this is the tetrahedron
right here I just got through the
insulating the outside of it with a
under spray under coating spray for
automotive vehicles Ottoman automobiles
will just set this inside here let you
see what this looks like
see if I can get it situated here I got
I need to I need to take a day and clean
this table off it's a mess I know but
that's what it looks like with it inside
there and as you can see it fits
precisely in there you can see where the
electric tape is contacting the
cardboard and when I hit the outer
exterior of the tetrahedron with high
voltage will it arced through and then
this is what I use right here just a
piece of copper wire I've bent and then
I press it down over that and that keeps
it closed and this is what I've been
energizing it with is my NST six
thousand volts maximum and I've done all
different kinds I've tried I've tried
rectifying halfway bridge rectification
tried doing a see through it I tried
putting a I thought putting pancake coil
like this inserting it in the center
right here for a primary and then it
trying to energize the coil via this as
a primary and so far my best results
have been hitting the detector ahed Hren
with high voltage energizing the
tetrahedron with high voltage and the I
think the basis of operation this is
single wire energy transfer I believe
there is no positive negative coming off
the space time antenna there's one wire
comes off the antenna and that's that is
your
that is your power and then that goes to
load now as you can see I've built a
every Minko plug here and that's what I
put on the I put that on the single wire
coming off of the off of the STA and
then I come off of that come off the
positive and the negative and I went to
an old dead completely dead battery and
I charged it for maybe an hour and I had
to put just plain tap water in it I
didn't have any distilled tap water I
didn't have any acid to put in it the
battery was completely dry and I hid
that for about an hour and I brought
this battery up that was completely dead
no acid back up to 5 volts and it's been
standing there for about a day with now
that really that really shocks me I mean
what you think about it if it'll do that
to a completely dead battery what would
it do to a deep cycle battery for
keeping it charged
so possibilities are looking good here
for single wire transmission with an
avro Minko plug the next video I'll try
to hook this thing up with my NST there
and we'll see if we can't make some
sparks through that spark gap and I'll
show you what this thing will do the
last time I had it up in a running I had
a 5 watt LED bulb threaded into this and
I think I ran I didn't go through the
plug though I came off with a single
wire coming from the STA went through
the bulb and then to ground and the bulb
would
it would flash about three pulses pulses
about three pulses a second and I'll
show you that in the next video try to
fire it up see how good I can do how
good a job I can do that it with one
hand
man in the camera and the other one men
and the gauges but I will say this if
you try to build this order caution to
the wise don't put any digital gauges on
the Agra Minko plug to check voltage i
fried two digital multimeters one cheap
one one el cheapo like this and one good
Clint meter like that trying to check
voltage I don't know if it's the
frequency I don't know if it's the
voltage but I recommend an analog I
checked with an analog meter like this
and I was measuring like 360 volts DC
that's no smoothing capacitor or
anything that's straight out of the ever
Minko plug and I was getting three
hundred and sixty volts DC and I'm
assuming that's probably pulse DC since
there was no smoothing capacitor or
anything not sure how that works on an
Avro Minko plug but I'll tell you I'm
running out of time on this video but
I'll tell you a little bit more about
some experiments that I've done and
we'll fire this baby up on the next
video and we'll talk to you some more
then later
till next time